William "Andy" Barringer

(509) 514-0825 | wabarringer@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/william-barringer-9a615566

SUMMARY

A customer service expert with 6 years of experience with phone support, data entry, and helping clients in difficult situations. Proficient at authentically connecting with individuals in order to best deliver satisfaction and peace of mind. Skilled at problem solving and adapting in ever-changing work environments.

EXPERIENCE

Liberty Mutual Insurance | Liberty Lake, WA Claims Customer Service Representative | Dec. 2015 - Dec. 2021

Job Description

- Act as first point of contact for Liberty Mutual policy holders
- File new auto, home and liability claims for policy holders, claimants and agents
- Set up services for customers, e.g., rental vehicles, towing, inspections, salvage, water mitigation, window and door board-up, and theft protection
- Resolve various issues with existing claims, e.g., payments, reporting fraud, tracking status, troubleshooting systems, and general consulting
- Educate customers on digital applications, Liberty Mutual's website and filling out online forms

Work Related Responsibilities

- Establish a customer connection by conveying a calm and compassionate attitude.
- Make it easy for policyholders by providing the information that they need
- Adhere to state specific regulations, and stay up to date with extreme weather events and current changes
- Collect as much detailed information as necessary and thoroughly note each claim
- Successfully deescalate situations by taking ownership of the call
- Resolve each customer's need quickly while maintaining efficiency

Atlas Staffing | Spokane, WA Warehouse Associate | 2014 – 2015

Keihn's Floor Covering | Spokane, WA Flooring Installer | 2013 – 2014

EDUCATION

Medical Lake High School High School Diploma | Graduated 2009

Spokane Falls Community College
Associates in Applied Science | Graduated 2012